<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Welcome to My Website!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome to My Website!</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:58:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Li-Fraumeni Syndrome (LFS)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:58:23 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lfs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Li-Fraumeni Syndrome (LFS) is a rare, inherited disorder that significantly increases the risk of developing various types of cancer, often at a young age. It’s caused by mutations in the TP53 gene, a crucial tumor suppressor, making affected individuals more susceptible to cancers like breast cancer, sarcomas, brain tumors, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Working on LFS has been an eye-opening experience. The complexity of the genetic mutations and their effects on cancer risk continue to challenge researchers, but it also provides a unique opportunity to explore innovative approaches to cancer risk prediction. Wang Lab is particularly focused on using real clinical data to improve risk prediction models for individuals with LFS, specifically in predicting TP53 mutations and the onset of multiple primary cancers (LFSPRO). There is hope that early detection and personalized interventions can improve outcomes for those affected. I look forward to sharing more updates as we continue to delve deeper into this important area.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joining MD Anderson Cancer Center</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 14:43:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, I embarked on an exciting new journey at MD Anderson Cancer Center. I’m eager to collaborate with the incredible researchers and clinicians here and contribute to groundbreaking cancer research. It’s a dynamic environment with so much to explore, and I’m excited to be part of this community, working towards advancing cancer care and making a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;mdanderson.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;MD Anderson Cancer Center&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
